export const questions = [
    {
    id:"1",
    question: "What is TM Money Transfer?",
    answer: "TM Money Transfer is a mobile payments service that allows people to make real-time money transfers to mobile money and other local financial institutions from all over the world to registered mobile money/other available financial institution users in Rwanda, Uganda, Kenya, Tanzania, Burundi, DRC Congo, Malawi and Zambia and South Korea.",
    },
    {
    id:"2",
    question: "How can I transfer money with TM Money Transfer?",
    answer: "To transfer money, you must open an account, sign in and follow the transfer indications. You can also transfer money anonymously with some disadvantages like your records will not be saved. You won't find transaction history in your dashboard, and the receiver contact won't be saved in your phonebook for future use. Please consider signing in first, if you need high security and any of the above benefits.",
    },
    {
    id:"3",
    question: "Which country can I transfer money to?",
    answer: "Till now we are transferring money to Rwanda, Uganda, Kenya, Tanzania, Burundi, DRC Congo, Malawi, Zambia, and South Korea.",
    },
    {
    id:"4",
    question: "How long does it take for the money to be delivered?",
    answer: "Once the payment has been made it takes less than 5 minutes for the transaction to be completed. After sending make sure you check your email and confirm the delivery receipt.",
    },
    {
    id:"5",
    question: "How does TM Money Transfer work?",
    answer: "TM Money Transfer allows users to link their bank accounts, credit cards, and debit cards to their TM Money Transfer account and then use TM Money Transfer to send and receive payments online, without having to share their financial information.",
    },
    {
    id:"6",
    question: "How can I contact TM Money Transfer?",
    answer: "You can contact us via all available mobile numbers, and social media platforms, and by reaching our branches. ",
    },
    {
    id:"7",
    question: "What fees does TM Money Transfer charge?",
    answer: "TM Money Transfer charges a fee for some transactions, such as receiving payments for goods and services. The fee is typically 2.5% per transaction, although it may slightly vary based on the type of transaction and the user's location.",
    },
    {
    id:"8",
    question: "Is TM Money Transfer secure?",
    answer: "Yes, TM Money Transfer is considered a secure platform for online payments. It uses advanced encryption technology to protect user information and offers additional security features such as two-factor authentication.",
    },
    {
    id:"9",
    question: "Can TM Money Transfer be used internationally?",
    answer: "Yes, TM Money Transfer can be used to send money to over 10 countries from all over the world. However, fees and restrictions may slightly vary based on the user's location.",
    },
    {
    id:"10",
    question: "What customer support does TM Money Transfer offer?",
    answer: "TM Money Transfer offers customer support through its online Help&suppport Center, email support, and phone support. It also offers a chatbot feature for quick answers to frequently asked questions.",
    },
    {
    id:"11",
    question: "Can TM Money Transfer be used for nonprofit donations?",
    answer: "Yes, TM Money Transfer offers a discounted transaction rate for registered nonprofit organizations and allows them to accept donations through its platform. ",
    },
    ];